<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lab3Mobile</string>
    <string name="day1_header">Sleep Without Guilt</string>
    <string name="day1_short_desc">Rest is not a reward for exhaustion. It is a basic need.</string>
    <string name="day1_long_desc">A cat never apologizes for taking a nap in the middle of the day or mentally keeps score of every hour spent resting. If you need to stop, lie down, and catch your breath, that is not weakness and not laziness. Sometimes the best way to keep going is to curl up for a while and recover first.</string>
    <string name="day2_header">Find the Sunny Spot</string>
    <string name="day2_short_desc">Move toward what feels warmer, calmer, and kinder.</string>
    <string name="day2_long_desc">A cat will always find the place that feels cozy, warm, and just right. That is not pickiness — it is a talent for choosing well. Life works the same way. Pay attention to your own “sunny spots”: people, places, habits, and activities that make things feel lighter. Do not ignore what warms you.</string>
    <string name="day3_header">Don’t Chase Every Noise</string>
    <string name="day3_short_desc">Not everything deserves your attention, worry, or energy.</string>
    <string name="day3_long_desc">Cats are curious, but they do not treat every little sound like a life-or-death emergency. People often get tired because they try to respond to absolutely everything: every message, every request, every problem. Not every noise deserves your energy. Some things can simply stay in the background.</string>
    <string name="day4_header">Choose a Comfortable Place</string>
    <string name="day4_short_desc">You do not have to stay uncomfortable just because you are used to it.</string>
    <string name="day4_long_desc">If a cat feels uncomfortable, it gets up and leaves. It does not sit there heroically enduring something cold, cramped, or unpleasant. There is wisdom in that. You do not have to remain in conversations, routines, or situations that make you feel bad just because “that’s how it is.” Sometimes the best choice is simply to move.</string>
    <string name="day5_header">Stretch Gracefully</string>
    <string name="day5_short_desc">Sometimes the best thing you can do is slow down and feel your body again.</string>
    <string name="day5_long_desc">After sleeping, a cat always stretches — carefully, beautifully, and without rushing. It is a reminder that the body needs more than just effort; it needs care too. Pause for a moment, roll your shoulders, breathe out, and loosen your back. One small movement can bring you back to yourself better than another cup of coffee.</string>
    <string name="day6_header">Don’t Trust Everyone Right Away</string>
    <string name="day6_short_desc">Watch first. Let people closer only when it feels right.</string>
    <string name="day6_long_desc">A cat rarely opens up immediately. First it watches, sniffs, and pays attention to tone and intention. That is not coldness — it is healthy caution. You are allowed to do the same: not trust too quickly, not share too much, and not rush closeness. It is better to build trust slowly and solidly than fast and carelessly.</string>
    <string name="day7_header">Love Selectively</string>
    <string name="day7_short_desc">Real affection does not have to be spread equally to everyone.</string>
    <string name="day7_long_desc">Cats do not try to win over every single person, but they know how to become deeply attached to the ones they choose. That is a good lesson too. You do not have to give your warmth to everyone out of obligation. It is far more valuable to protect your sincerity and invest it where you can truly be yourself.</string>
    <string name="day8_header">Leave When It’s No Longer Fun</string>
    <string name="day8_short_desc">You are allowed to stop what no longer brings you joy.</string>
    <string name="day8_long_desc">If a cat loses interest, it simply walks away. No long explanations, no dramatic speeches. Sometimes you should do the same: step out of pointless arguments, end boring conversations, and let go of things that have clearly run their course. Not everything has to be dragged out to the bitter end.</string>
    <string name="day9_header">Purr at What Is Yours</string>
    <string name="day9_short_desc">Notice the small things that bring you quiet joy.</string>
    <string name="day9_long_desc">A cat expresses pleasure honestly and simply: warmth, food, affection, a favorite place — and suddenly there is purring. Humans often let joy disappear under hurry and seriousness. Allow yourself to notice the small good things and stop dismissing them. Happiness is not always loud. Very often, it just hums softly beside you.</string>
    <string name="day10_header">Sharpen Your Claws on the Problem</string>
    <string name="day10_short_desc">Turn irritation into action instead of letting it build inside you.</string>
    <string name="day10_long_desc">When a cat needs to release tension, it sharpens its claws. Not for philosophical reasons — simply because it works. Your version of a scratching post might be a walk, exercise, cleaning, journaling, a good conversation, or one concrete step toward solving the problem. It is better to leave a mark on the issue than on your own nervous system.</string>
    <string name="day11_header">Don’t Get in the Way of Your Own Rest</string>
    <string name="day11_short_desc">Stop turning rest into another task filled with guilt.</string>
    <string name="day11_long_desc">A cat never worries about whether it is “resting productively enough.” It simply rests. Meanwhile, a person can lie down and still keep arguing internally, planning, blaming themselves, and worrying. If you are resting, then really rest. Otherwise it is not a break — it is just exhaustion in a horizontal position.</string>
    <string name="day12_header">Be Soft, but Have Claws</string>
    <string name="day12_short_desc">Kindness does not cancel boundaries or self-protection.</string>
    <string name="day12_long_desc">A cat can be affectionate, warm, and comforting — right up until someone handles it carelessly. Then it quickly reminds everyone that soft paws still have sharp claws. You can be kind too and still say no, protect your boundaries, and refuse to let people take advantage of you.</string>
    <string name="day13_header">Don’t Explain Every Step</string>
    <string name="day13_short_desc">Sometimes it is enough to know why you are doing something.</string>
    <string name="day13_long_desc">A cat never gives a report on why it suddenly sat in a box, disappeared under the bed, or started staring at the wall. It simply has its reasons. You do not need to justify every decision to everyone either. Not everything requires an explanation, especially when it comes to your comfort and peace of mind.</string>
    <string name="day14_header">Explore New Things Carefully</string>
    <string name="day14_short_desc">Curiosity is good, as long as it does not erase your sense of safety.</string>
    <string name="day14_long_desc">A cat explores the unfamiliar carefully: step closer, look, sniff, step back, then return. That is an excellent life strategy too. You do not have to dive headfirst into every new opportunity. Sometimes it is wiser to approach gradually, keeping your curiosity without losing your footing.</string>
    <string name="day15_header">Find Your Box</string>
    <string name="day15_short_desc">Sometimes happiness lives in something simple, small, and imperfect.</string>
    <string name="day15_long_desc">You can buy a cat an expensive bed, and it will still choose the cardboard box. That is a reminder that comfort and joy do not always look impressive. Sometimes your version of “perfect” is not trendy — it is simple, familiar, and real. Do not be embarrassed by the small place that makes you feel safe.</string>
    <string name="day16_header">Look Out the Window</string>
    <string name="day16_short_desc">Pausing to observe is part of life, not a waste of it.</string>
    <string name="day16_long_desc">A cat can sit at the window for ages, looking completely absorbed in the important task of observing the world. Honestly, it has a point. Not every minute has to be useful in a measurable way. Sometimes you just need to look around, let your eyes rest on something far away, and remember that the world is bigger than your current worries.</string>
    <string name="day17_header">Ask for Affection When You’re Ready</string>
    <string name="day17_short_desc">Closeness works best when it is chosen freely and at the right time.</string>
    <string name="day17_long_desc">A cat decides for itself when it wants warmth, attention, and contact. There is dignity in that. You are allowed to manage your own distance too: you do not have to be constantly available, force social energy you do not have, or show up emotionally before you are ready.</string>
    <string name="day18_header">Don’t Make Unnecessary Sudden Moves</string>
    <string name="day18_short_desc">Calmness is often more effective than panic and hurry.</string>
    <string name="day18_long_desc">A cat can stay completely still for a long time, then make one perfectly timed jump. People often do the opposite: lots of frantic movement, very little result. Sometimes it is better not to rush around but to wait, assess the moment, and make one right move instead of ten chaotic ones.</string>
    <string name="day19_header">Remember You Are Not a Toy</string>
    <string name="day19_short_desc">You are not here to entertain, rescue, or stay convenient all the time.</string>
    <string name="day19_long_desc">Even the sweetest cat eventually makes it clear that it cannot be poked, carried around, and used according to someone else’s mood forever. The same goes for people. You are not a function for someone else’s comfort. Your value is not in being easy to use. It is in being a real person with needs, limits, and a life of your own.</string>
    <string name="day20_header">Eat With Respect for Yourself</string>
    <string name="day20_short_desc">Caring for yourself begins with the simplest things.</string>
    <string name="day20_long_desc">A cat never treats food like some random detail of the day. For a cat, it matters. That is a good reminder for you too: food, water, sleep, and fresh air are not minor things. A surprising number of “complicated crises” feel a little more manageable once you have eaten properly.</string>
    <string name="day21_header">Wash the Day Off</string>
    <string name="day21_short_desc">Do not carry everything forward when some of it can be let go.</string>
    <string name="day21_long_desc">After a busy day, a cat grooms itself as if brushing the noise of the world right out of its fur. You need your own version of that ritual too: a shower, silence, music, journaling, or a short walk. Not everything that happened today needs to come with you into tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="day22_header">Don’t Rush for Approval</string>
    <string name="day22_short_desc">Your worth does not increase every time you try to please someone.</string>
    <string name="day22_long_desc">A cat does not build its entire personality around being approved of — and that is part of its strength. It does not try to become easier, funnier, or more convenient just to be liked. That is a useful position for you too. Do not keep reshaping yourself endlessly just to make it easier for others to accept you. The right people will value the real thing.</string>
    <string name="day23_header">Master the Art of Silence</string>
    <string name="day23_short_desc">Not every thought must be spoken, and not every argument must continue.</string>
    <string name="day23_long_desc">A cat knows how to be silent in a very expressive way. Sometimes simple presence is stronger than a long explanation. People can do that too: not answer immediately, not get pulled into something pointless, not defend themselves where nobody truly wants to listen. Silence is not always weakness. Sometimes it is a very precise kind of strength.</string>
    <string name="day24_header">Balance Tenderness and Independence</string>
    <string name="day24_short_desc">You can love closeness without losing yourself.</string>
    <string name="day24_long_desc">A cat knows how to be near someone without dissolving into them completely. It keeps its own personality, habits, and paths. That is an important reminder: love, friendship, and attachment should not require the disappearance of who you are. Being close does not mean becoming less yourself.</string>
    <string name="day25_header">Land on Your Feet</string>
    <string name="day25_short_desc">Even after a mistake, you can regain your balance.</string>
    <string name="day25_long_desc">Cats are symbols of agility for a reason: they know how to recover quickly after awkwardness, surprises, or falls. Life works the same way. What matters is not never making mistakes, but knowing how to steady yourself again afterward. You stumbled — fine. What matters is that you can recover and keep going.</string>
    <string name="day26_header">Don’t Step Into Water Without a Reason</string>
    <string name="day26_short_desc">Challenge is not worth accepting just because it is “good for you.”</string>
    <string name="day26_long_desc">A cat sees no reason to step into something cold, wet, and unpleasant if it can avoid it. There is a kind of anti-heroic wisdom in that. Not every struggle makes you better. Sometimes maturity means not enduring discomfort for the sake of a dramatic idea, but honestly choosing what truly suits you.</string>
    <string name="day27_header">Protect Your Quiet Place</string>
    <string name="day27_short_desc">Everyone needs a space where they can recover in peace.</string>
    <string name="day27_long_desc">A cat always has a corner to retreat to when it wants silence. That is not running away from the world — it is self-preservation. You need your own quiet place too, whether physical or internal. A room, headphones, a walk, a book, a few minutes without people. Something that helps you become yourself again.</string>
    <string name="day28_header">Don’t Forget to Play</string>
    <string name="day28_short_desc">Seriousness should not push out liveliness and curiosity.</string>
    <string name="day28_long_desc">Even the most dignified cat can suddenly start chasing a scrap of paper, a shadow, or its own imagination. And honestly, good for it. Adult life does not improve by eliminating play entirely. Do something just for fun, delight, laughter, or lightness. That is not childish — it is one way to stay alive inside.</string>
    <string name="day29_header">Accept Love, Even If You Pretend You Don’t Need It</string>
    <string name="day29_short_desc">Sometimes warmth is already there. You just have to stop dodging it.</string>
    <string name="day29_long_desc">Cats know how to look independent and still come closer when they want warmth. People do that too: pretending they can handle everything alone even when they need support. Letting yourself receive care is nothing to be ashamed of. Sometimes strength is not in total independence, but in honesty.</string>
    <string name="day30_header">Be Yourself Like Royalty</string>
    <string name="day30_short_desc">Do not make yourself smaller. Even your strangeness can be magnificent.</string>
    <string name="day30_long_desc">A cat never doubts its right to sit in the middle of a room as if the whole place belongs to it. That is the final lesson. You do not need to become quieter, smaller, or easier to deserve your place in the world. Take up your space calmly, confidently, and without unnecessary apologies.</string>
</resources>